{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267447952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267447952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267455867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267455867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267470443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267470442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267476781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267476780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267518349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267518349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267557132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267557132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-15-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267563419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267563419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-15-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267569366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267569366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-15"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267578247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267578246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-6-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267586962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267586962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-6-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267619259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267619258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267626303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267626303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-3-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267645703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267645703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267652343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267652342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 0b87c271-6030-467c-ae29-5954e0165171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267712314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267712314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 390a8947-7445-44d0-9c0b-18ab32b6aa07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kimya_tamu-vya-kimya-chako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kimya"," userResponse":" kimya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267734625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267734623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 390a8947-7445-44d0-9c0b-18ab32b6aa07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kimya_tamu-vya-kimya-chako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267734714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267734713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" 390a8947-7445-44d0-9c0b-18ab32b6aa07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267747171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267747171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-B-CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267751769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267751769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_F-A-U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267756188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267756187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_J-A-H"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267760315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267760315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-K-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267766296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267766296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-H-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267770363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267770363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-N-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267774250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267774250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-M-B"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267779064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267779064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_Y-M-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267782806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267782805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_R-A-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267786821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267786821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-A-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267792569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267792567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" b96534aa-5004-4a88-be77-81bb70faa782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-A-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267806652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267806652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267815594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267815594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-15-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267821626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267821626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267829538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267829538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267845276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267845276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-15"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267857625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267857625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267875097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267875096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548268540938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548268540937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-6-14"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548268778221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548268778221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_211709"," gameId":" edac57fa-cd0c-40b1-abb6-38058cb9815c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-3-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}